<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Source on Incubyte Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/categories/open-source/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Source on Incubyte Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 Incubyte - All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:10:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.incubyte.co/categories/open-source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Five Git Tricks To Make Crafting Software Easier</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/five-git-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:10:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/five-git-tricks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Git is the most widely used version control system in the world and it is something that every Software Craftsperson should master.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to contribute to open-source project: A beginner&#39;s guide</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-project-a-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/how-to-contribute-to-open-source-project-a-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a first-time contributor? Are you wondering how to start contributing to OSS? Well, this guide is made for you. Hopefully, you are reading this because you are looking to take the first step toward making an open-source contribution! You’ve been using multiple Open-Source projects and have read many articles, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.incubyte.co/benefits-and-challenges-of-open-source-development/&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; introduction to Open-Source Software. You’ve been sold on the idea and can’t wait to start! Only, how do you even begin? How do you decide on the right project? What happens if something goes wrong? This can be a bit intimidating at first. No need to worry though.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benefits and Challenges of Open-Source Development</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/benefits-and-challenges-of-open-source-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/benefits-and-challenges-of-open-source-development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Open-source software (OSS) is the holy grail for developers. It is a hub of innovation through intense collaboration in this era of agile software development. Without it, many of the technologies we take for granted today would never have been developed or would have been locked away behind strict patents. The open-source movement is the reason technology has developed at such a breakneck pace over the past few decades.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
