<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Playbook on Incubyte Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/categories/playbook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Playbook on Incubyte Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 Incubyte - All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:10:20 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.incubyte.co/categories/playbook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Its 2025 And You Should Not Write Code Without Tests</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/its-2025-and-you-should-not-write-code-without-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:10:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/its-2025-and-you-should-not-write-code-without-tests/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 2025, shipping code without tests should be a total no. In a landscape where deployments happen multiple times a day and services are expected to be available 24/7, undetected regressions can lead to downtime and erode user trust. Automated tests provide a safety net that ensures changes don’t introduce unexpected behavior, offering confidence and stability as applications evolve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Translations in Rails: Why Constants Can’t Adapt to Locale Changes and How to Fix It?</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/rails-dynamic-translation-constants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:35:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/rails-dynamic-translation-constants/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In math and science a particular number or value that does not change is called a constant. In programming too, a constant typically represents a value that doesn’t change — a number, string, or any data type that remains the same throughout the application’s runtime. But what if you need to assign a dynamic, changing value to a constant? Can a constant, by its nature, ever be dynamic?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Ownership: The Catalyst for Achieving Professional Excellence</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/extreme-ownership-catalyst-for-achieving-professional-excellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/extreme-ownership-catalyst-for-achieving-professional-excellence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the realm of software craftsmanship and professional development, certain values stand out as pillars of success. These include extreme ownership, relentless pursuit of quality with pragmatism, proactive collaboration, active pursuit of mastery, inviting and giving feedback effectively, and creating ecstatic customers. These are the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.incubyte.co/post/succeeding-at-incubyte-our-core-values&#34;&gt;guiding principles&lt;/a&gt; that we adhere to at Incubyte. At the core of these values lies a principle that serves as a catalyst for achieving them: &lt;strong&gt;extreme ownership.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interviewing Software Craftspeople: How to Get it Right!</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/interviewing-software-craftspeople/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:00:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/interviewing-software-craftspeople/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When you’re hiring talented software developers, the interview process is more than just a skills assessment—it’s your chance to show them that your team is a place where they can truly grow and make an impact.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chandrayaan 3 TDD Assessment</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/chandrayaan-3-tdd-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:04:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/chandrayaan-3-tdd-assessment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A Software Craftsperson at Incubyte is a person who has a strong commitment to the craft of software development. Someone who is passionate about software, knows her/his tools well and is able to use them effectively to create carefully crafted software. Ultimately, a person who has a strong sense of what it is they are doing and is self-motivated to learn and grow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angular Provider</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/angular-provider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 12:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/angular-provider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Angular Provider is like a command to Angular Dependency Injection system regarding how to get an object/instance for a particular dependency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnings From Terraform</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/learnings-from-terraform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:52:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/learnings-from-terraform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Terraform is infrastructure as a code. I know it is a fancy word but here is the meaning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnings From Clean Code</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/learnings-from-clean-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 11:55:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/learnings-from-clean-code/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Robert Martin, fondly known as “Uncle Bob” in our community, is a software engineer and more famously an author and one of the founding fathers of Software Craftsmanship movement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Code Coverage Should Not Be Your Measure of Reliability</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/code-coverage-and-reliability/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 22:58:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/code-coverage-and-reliability/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Code coverage is a measure (in percentage) of the degree to which the source code of a program is executed wh­en a particular test suite is run.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Kickstart Checklist</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/kickstart-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/kickstart-checklist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://atulgawande.com/book/the-checklist-manifesto/&#34;&gt;Checklist Manifesto&lt;/a&gt; by Atul Gawande, walks us through the benefits of the humble checklist. He talks about how checklists of &amp;ldquo;dumb stuff&amp;rdquo; can save us from disasters in life and death situations. We developers, too, can use such a checklist when we start a new project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Year Of Pandemic &amp; One Year Of Incubyte</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/one-year-of-incubyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/one-year-of-incubyte/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It all started when— unbeknownst to the world, a series of lockdowns changed the way India Inc. operated. The world hit a big fast-forward button to the future of remote work. And right around that time, in February of 2020, a small team that called itself Incubyte set out on its own mission in this new normal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Onboarding &amp; Immersion at Incubyte</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/remote-onboarding-and-immersion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/remote-onboarding-and-immersion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Employee onboarding is the important process of introducing newly hired employees to the organisation. It is everything that leads up to the employee&amp;rsquo;s total immersion into the organisation&amp;rsquo;s culture. An effective onboarding process helps the new employee relate better with the company values and helps them get up and running quicker. Immersion is the process of creating a common future and common purpose for all employees by aligning expectation, values, purpose, mission and goals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Incubyte?</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/why-incubyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/why-incubyte/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quality is usually an implicit requirement when it comes to developing software. Users ask for a beautiful UI, outstanding performance, and the functionality they need, but quality is never on the list - it is just expected! And because it is so, it is often overlooked. Users end up getting only what was explicitly stated.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Hire Software Craftspeople</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/hiring-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/hiring-process/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Any organization is the sum of its people and employees are its main spokespeople. Human capital is our most valued asset. So, hiring suitable candidates, who share the same values and core principles as Incubyte is our biggest imperative.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feedback &amp; Rapid Prototyping</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/feedback/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;No fixed direction remains valid for long&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;-&lt;/em&gt; Extreme Programming Explained by Kent Beck&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning &amp; Communication</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/planning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of our primary process goals is to make frequent, small releases of our working software. We do this through regular communication and bi-weekly iterations on a product.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology Platforms &amp; Business Economics</title>
      <link>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/technology-platforms-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.incubyte.co/blog/technology-platforms-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Early in a project, we have to decide which platforms we&amp;rsquo;ll use. Which platforms depend on our ideas for solving the users&amp;rsquo; problems. After considering what&amp;rsquo;s best for users, the best tools for us have a strong community, make us happy, and help us create and iterate quickly. Our developers are highly versatile with their choice of tools and integrate the tools&amp;rsquo; ideologies into their development process.Some of the tools we use and platforms we work with (and highly recommend) are/Some of the ideologies that our choice of tech platforms abide by are:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
